How have you been using AI
in your school work?
Umm, I use it to help me summarize lecture notes and
I use it sometimes when I don't
understand the math problem.
Nice
What about you?
I use it as a tool for a lot of my design processes.
I
I use it to help me brainstorm ideas
I use it to
help me speed up
wireframes and help me prototype
umm my designs
Well that's very useful then
Yeah I think it's very useful
What kind of AI platforms do you use?
I mainly like to use Claude or ChatGPT
I use Claude more for prototyping and coding
How about you?
I use Gemini
What do you like about Gemini?
I like the way the website looks
it just looks very
minimalistic and clean
You like the UI of the website?
Yes
Nice